turntoislam.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy » Salamyou Muslim Social Network

Privacy Policy   
This privacy policy sets out how TurnToIslam uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using TurnToIslam products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, TurnToIslam.com and any associated websites and sub-domains. 

TurnToIslam may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes. 

What information we collect 

When using any products and services provided by TurnToIslam, we may require some or all of the following information: 

name   
email address   
information related to any financial transactions which may be carried out   
Additionally, whilst using the TurnToIslam.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected: 

Internet Protocol (IP) address   
geographical location   
browser type and version   
operating system   
referral source   
length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity   
What we do with the information we collect 

The information you provide to TurnToIslam is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons: 

internal record keeping   
access to the TurnToIslam.com website, associated websites and sub-domains   
account management   
account confirmation and account reset   
confirmation of email address   
sending notices of product upgrades, security alerts and patches, and other relevant communications 

We do not share any of your internal information such as emails, to any third party. 

How we use cookies and IP addresses 

TurnToIslam.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and your IP address. 

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use TurnToIslam.com and any associated websites and sub-domains. 

IP addresses of computers used to visit TurnToIslam.com and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question. 

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time. 

Links to other websites 

TurnToIslam.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with TurnToIslam 

TurnToIslam has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and TurnToIslam cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. 

Controlling your personal information 

When using the TurnToIslam, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account. We advise to test these features to your liking. 

TurnToIslam will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you security information, product updates, or other information pertaining to TurnToIslam, or your account. 

If you discover any of the information TurnToIslam holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made. We are also available to contact for any other issues:
